A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 4, Accession 2017:060 FA1442
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies, 1982-2005; 3
  - Board Proposal for the Luce Fund for Southeast Asian Studies Initiative, undated (Box 66, Folder 438)
  - Guidelines, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 439)
  - Grant Projects, 2005 (Box 66, Folder 440)
  - Grants Awarded, 1987-1991 (Box 66, Folder 441)
  - Southeast Asian Study Centers, 1986-1991 (Box 66, Folder 442)
  - Southeast Asian Libraries, 1989-1990 (Box 66, Folder 443)
  - Payment Schedules, 1987-1993 (Box 66, Folder 444)
  - List of University Coordinators, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 445)
  - Reviews and Reviewers (Round I), 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 446)
  - Grants Recommended (Round II), 1988 (Box 66, Folder 447)
  - Reviews and Reviewers (Round II), 1988-1989 (Box 66, Folder 448)
  - Grants Recommended (Round III), 1991 (Box 67, Folder 449)
  - Reviews and Reviewers (Round III), 1991 (Box 67, Folder 450)
  - LFSEAS Survey, 1990 (Box 67, Folder 451)
  - Wingspread Conference and Meetings on Southeast Asian Studies in the United States, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 452)
  - Arizona State University, 1987-1992 (Box 67, Folder 453)
  - Arizona State University - Library, 1991-1996 (Box 67, Folder 454)
  - Arizona State University - Round III, 1991-1995 (Box 67, Folder 455)
  - Cornell University, 1985-1992 (Box 67, Folder 456)
  - Cornell University - Reports on Grant I, 1988-1990 (Box 68, Folder 457)
  - Cornell University - Reports on Grant II, 1991-2004 (Box 68, Folder 458)
  - Cornell University - Library, 1989-1992 (Box 68, Folder 459)
  - Cornell University - Research, 1991-2000 (Box 68, Folder 460)
  - Northern Illinois University, 1984-1996 (Box 68, Folder 461-462)
  - Northwest Regional Consortium, 1982-1996 (Box 69, Folder 463-465)
  - Northwest Regional Consortium - Library Development Grant II, 1989-2002 (Box 69, Folder 466-467)
  - Northwest Regional Consortium - Round III, 1991-1993 (Box 69, Folder 468)
  - Ohio University - Faculty Positions in Economics, Philosophy, and Linguistics (Indonesian), Research Bibliographer, and Graduate Student Fellowships, 1991-2002 (Box 70, Folder 469-469A)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Environmental Science and Adaptive Strategies, 1986-1995 (Box 70, Folder 470-473)
  - University of Hawaii, 1986-1998 (Box 71, Folder 474-475)
  - University of Hawaii - "The Sago Complex in Maluku: Environmental, Socieo-Cultural and Developmental Implications" Research, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 476)
  - University of Michigan, 1987-1998 (Box 71, Folder 477-479)
  - University of Michigan - Popular Memories of Historic Transitions in Indonesia, 1991-2000 (Box 72, Folder 480)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1986-1995 (Box 72, Folder 481-483)
    Thai Language Proficiency Project, Consortium for Advanced Summer Thai (CAST), Acquisition of Southeast Asian Library Materials, Faculty Position in Agricultural Economics, and Southeast Asian Video Archive
  - University of Wisconsin - Poverty, Property, and Policy: Social and Economic Issues in the Conservation of Forest Resources in Thailand and the Philippines, 1991 (Box 72, Folder 484)
  - Yale University, 1986-1995 (Box 72, Folder 485-486)
- Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars, 1980-2005; 4
  The Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars was created to enhance the study of China in major American academic centers and encourage interaction between Chinese and American scholars. Each participating university was eligible to receive support for one scholar-in-residence from China for each academic year. The grants awarded were not competitive in nature, but were based on nominations from the universities.
  General program information can be found at the beginning of the series. Individual grant files can be found within university-specific sub-series.
  - Board Proposal for the Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars, 1989 (Box 73, Folder 487)
  - Evaluations, 1986-1987 (Box 73, Folder 488)
    Closed -- contains peer review materials.
  - Extension Approvals, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 489)
  - General Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box 73, Folder 490)
  - Grants Awarded, 2005 (Box 73, Folder 491)
  - Guidelines, 1984-1990 (Box 73, Folder 492)
  - Final Reports, 1982-1986 (Box 73, Folder 493)
  - Former Luce Chinese Scholars, 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 494)
  - Lists of Liaisons and Scholars, 1983-1984 (Box 73, Folder 495)
  - National Committee for United States-China Relations Orientation, 1982-1985 (Box 73, Folder 496)
  - Programs Similar to the Luce Fund for Chinese Scholars (General Information and Memos), 1984-1985 (Box 73, Folder 497)
  - Rejection Letters, 1989-1990 (Box 73, Folder 498)
  - Columbia University, 1981-1992; 1
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 74, Folder 499)
    - Yin Falu, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 500)
    - Wu Guoguang Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 501)
    - Ruan Ming, 1988-1991 (Box 74, Folder 502)
    - Gao Wangling, 1985-1992 (Box 74, Folder 503)
    - Lin Ying, 1985-1991 (Box 74, Folder 504)
    - He Zhaowu, 1983-1984 (Box 74, Folder 505)
  - Cornell University, 1981-1992; 2
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 74, Folder 506)
    - Dong Leshan, 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 507)
    - Hu Renzhi, 1984-1992 (Box 74, Folder 508)
    - Jia Qingguo Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 74, Folder 509)
    - Li Funing, 1984-1988 (Box 74, Folder 510)
    - Tien Jukang, 1982-1984 (Box 74, Folder 511)
    - Tien Jukang Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 74, Folder 512)
    - Wang Jiaxiang, 1986-1987 (Box 74, Folder 513)
    - Zhang Mengbai, 1984-1989 (Box 74, Folder 514)
  - Harvard University, 1980-1990; 3
    - General Correspondence, 1980-1989 (Box 75, Folder 515)
    - Chen Lai, 1986-1988 (Box 75, Folder 516)
    - Ji Shu-li Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 517)
    - Li Zhizhong, 1982-1984 (Box 75, Folder 518)
    - Lu Fan, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 519)
    - Luo Xiao-peng Extension, 1989 (Box 75, Folder 520)
    - Tang Ijie, 1983-1984 (Box 75, Folder 521)
    - Zhang Lei, 1985-1988 (Box 75, Folder 522)
    - Zhu Jiaming Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 75, Folder 523)
  - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies, 1981-1989; 4
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 75, Folder 524)
    - Ding Xinghao, 1983-1986 (Box 75, Folder 525)
    - He Weiling, 1986-1988 (Box 75, Folder 526)
    - Huang Fangyi, 1985-1986 (Box 75, Folder 527)
    - Wang Shaoren, 1987-1988 (Box 75, Folder 528)
    - Zhu Peixing, 1982-1986 (Box 75, Folder 529)
  - Michigan State University, 1983-1991; 5
    - General Correspondence, 1980-1992 (Box 75, Folder 530)
    - An Qi, 1984-1986 (Box 75, Folder 531)
    - Ma Zhizhou, 1985-1987 (Box 75, Folder 532)
    - Tsou Mingteh Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 75, Folder 533)
    - Wang Qingcheng, 1983-1984 (Box 76, Folder 534)
    - Wang Xi, 1986-1989 (Box 76, Folder 535)
    - Yao Shimou, 1983-1992 (Box 76, Folder 536)
  - Princeton University, 1981-1989; 6
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 76, Folder 537)
    - Li Honglin, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 538)
    - Wang Quanlum, 1982-1983 (Box 76, Folder 539)
    - Wang Yuquan, 1981-1983 (Box 76, Folder 540)
    - Xiao Ping, 1984 (Box 76, Folder 541)
    - Xu Pingfang, 1985-1987 (Box 76, Folder 542)
    - Xu Shuofang, 1983-1984 (Box 76, Folder 543)
  - Stanford University, 1980-1992; 7
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1992 (Box 76, Folder 544)
    - Jin Weinuo, 1987-1989 (Box 76, Folder 545)
    - Mi Hedu Extension, 1980-1992 (Box 76, Folder 546)
    - Tian Yuqing, 1984-1989 (Box 76, Folder 547)
    - Yan Siguang, 1990-1991 (Box 76, Folder 548)
    - Yan Jiayan, 1986-1989 (Box 76, Folder 549)
    - Yang Guozhen, 1985-1989 (Box 76, Folder 550)
    - Wang Guangsen, 1982-1985 (Box 76, Folder 551)
    - Zhang Jialin Extension, 1989-1992 (Box 76, Folder 552)
  - Tufts University, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, 1981-1991; 8
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 76, Folder 553)
    - Gao Shuyi, 1985-1986 (Box 76, Folder 554)
    - Jiang Zejun, 1981-1986 (Box 76, Folder 555)
    - Liang Zhousheng, 1984-1986 (Box 77, Folder 556)
    - Ni Yaoli, 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 557)
    - Shao Yijun Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 77, Folder 558)
    - Zhuang Qubing, 1986-1987 (Box 77, Folder 559)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1981-1993; 9
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1991 (Box 77, Folder 560)
    - Dong Shizhong Extension, 1989-1993 (Box 77, Folder 561)
    - Feng Shengbao Extension, 1990-1992 (Box 77, Folder 562)
    - Guo Wuxin, 1982-1984 (Box 77, Folder 563)
    - Lian Shaoming, 1986-1988 (Box 77, Folder 564)
    - Liao Ben Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 77, Folder 565)
    - Pang Pu, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 566)
    - Wu Xiaoling, 1985-1987 (Box 77, Folder 567)
    - Yang Xin, 1983-1989 (Box 77, Folder 568)
    - Zhou Yiliang, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 569)
  - University of California, Los Angeles, 1981-1990; 10
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 77, Folder 570)
    - Gao Ming, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 571)
    - Qi Mingcong, 1984-1985 (Box 77, Folder 572)
    - Su Bai, 1981-1983 (Box 77, Folder 573)
    - Xu Xinuw, 1986-1988 (Box 77, Folder 574)
    - Ye Xian'en, 1983-1984 (Box 77, Folder 575)
    - Wang Xiaoqiang Extension (Cancelled), 1990 (Box 77, Folder 576)
  - University of Chicago, 1981-1992; 11
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 78, Folder 577)
    - Chen Guanlie, 1983-1984 (Box 78, Folder 578)
    - Huang Shengzhang, 1983-1992 (Box 77, Folder 579)
    - Jing Qicheng, 1985-1991 (Box 78, Folder 580)
    - Li Gengjun, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 581)
    - Liu Yuehua Extension (Cancelled), 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 582)
    - Xiang Qing, 1984-1986 (Box 78, Folder 583)
    - Zhou Shiqiu, 1982-1984 (Box 78, Folder 584)
  - University of Michigan, 1981-1991; 12
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 78, Folder 585)
    - Chen Baosen, 1983-1985 (Box 78, Folder 586)
    - Chou Liquan, 1982-1984 (Box 78, Folder 587)
    - Hong Junyan, 1986-1988 (Box 78, Folder 588)
    - Lin Shuchung, 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 589)
    - Ruan Ming Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 78, Folder 590)
    - Wang Rongsheng, 1982-1983 (Box 78, Folder 591)
    - Zhao Fusan Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 592)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1981-1991; 13
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 78, Folder 593)
    - Chen Xiaoyu, 1985-1987 (Box 78, Folder 594)
    - Fan Dainian Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 78, Folder 595)
    - Guan Dedong, 1983-1989 (Box 78, Folder 596)
    - Jin Guantao, 1986-1987 (Box 78, Folder 597)
    - Lin Shiyu, 1982-1986 (Box 78, Folder 598)
    - Liu Yongquan Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 79, Folder 599)
    - Pan Jixing, 1981-1982 (Box 79, Folder 600)
    - Wang Ning Sheng, 1983-1985 (Box 79, Folder 601)
    - Zhang Guang-da Extension (Cancelled), 1990 (Box 79, Folder 602)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1989-1993; 14
    - General Correspondence - Extension, 1989-1993 (Box 79, Folder 603)
    - Tong Enzheng Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 604)
    - Zhang Xuejun Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 79, Folder 605)
  - University of Southern California, 1981-1993; 15
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 79, Folder 606)
    - Feng Huazhan, 1982-1985 (Box 79, Folder 607)
    - Li Daokui, 1982-1986 (Box 79, Folder 608)
    - Li Youyi, 1981-1985 (Box 79, Folder 609)
    - Pang Xiong, 1985-1988 (Box 79, Folder 610)
    - Peng Fei Extension, 1990 (Box 79, Folder 611)
    - Wang Chengxu, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 612)
    - Wu Tianming Extension, 1987-1993 (Box 79, Folder 613)
    - Xie Fei, 1986-1990 (Box 79, Folder 614)
  - University of Washington, 1981-1991; 16
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 79, Folder 615)
    - Cai Shaoqing, 1984-1986 (Box 79, Folder 616)
    - Chang Chungli, 1986-1984 (Box 79, Folder 617)
    - Ho Tzu-chuan, 1986-1991 (Box 79, Folder 618)
    - Li Ling Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 79, Folder 619)
    - Peng Yilin Extension, 1990-1991 (Box 79, Folder 620)
    - Qiu Xigui, 1982-1984 (Box 80, Folder 621)
    - Yang Guanghui Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 80, Folder 622)
    - Zhang Huiying, 1986-1989 (Box 80, Folder 623)
  - University of Wisconsin, 1981-1990; 17
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1989 (Box 80, Folder 624)
    - Chan Ying, 1983-1984 (Box 80, Folder 625)
    - Chen Yupi, 1981-1984 (Box 80, Folder 626)
    - Chou Ju-ch'ang, 1986-1988 (Box 80, Folder 627)
    - Li Zehou, 1981-1984 (Box 80, Folder 628)
    - Lin Chun Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 80, Folder 629)
    - Liu Yongcheng, 1983-1986 (Box 80, Folder 630)
    - Qui Renzong Extension, 1989-1990 (Box 80, Folder 631)
    - Yao Zhong, 1984-1986 (Box 80, Folder 632)
  - Yale University, 1981-1992; 18
    - General Correspondence, 1981-1992 (Box 80, Folder 633)
    - Hu Ji, 1984-1985 (Box 80, Folder 634)
    - Tan Jian, 1988-1989 (Box 80, Folder 635)
    - Tan Jian Extension, 1989-1991 (Box 80, Folder 636)
    - Wang Wensheng, 1986-1988 (Box 80, Folder 637)
    - Yu Songching, 1983-1987 (Box 80, Folder 638)
    - Xu Bangdo (Cancelled), 1985-1986 (Box 80, Folder 639)
    - Yuan Jihui, 1982-1983 (Box 80, Folder 640)
    - Zhang Kaiyuan Extension, 1990-1992 (Box 80, Folder 641)